University of Connecticut 1989.0024
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Director of University Libraries, 1958-1994
  - Subseries C: Norman Stevens, 1979-1995
    - Flexible work week (Box 33)
    - Staff Handbook
    - Report of the Management Review and Analysis Program
    - Formal ULA Level Review Procedure
    - Student Assistants in ARL Libraries
    - Conducting an Effective Employment Interview
    - Report of Planning Process
    - Report of ACEP
    - Report of Government Public Department Task Force
    - Report of Research and Information Services Implementation Committee
    - State Job Descriptions
    - Report of Collections Planning Committee
    - FRS Manual
    - Workplace health, video display terminal (Box 34)
    - Work schedule policy
    - Strategic Plan, 1995
    - Environmental Scanning Team I, II, III
    - Strategic Planning - Regional Campuses
    - Workstation Ergonomics
    - Strategic Plan
    - Technical Services Reorganization, 1987 (Box 35)
    - Physical Maintenance Subgroup
    - Space Analysis Subgroup
    - Serials List, 1978
    - UConn Library Branches - General (Box 36)
    - Business Administration Library
    - Avery Point Library
    - Hartford Library
    - Health Center Library
    - West Hartford Library Consolidation
    - Law Library
    - MRAP Policy Committee (Box 37)
    - OCLC Steering Committee
    - MRAP Organization Committee
    - Library Faculty Liason Committee
    - MRAP Implementation Committee
    - Bylaws Revisions Committee
    - Masterton Committee
    - Interagency Planning
    - MRAP Communication Committee
    - Cataloging Advisory Committee
    - Wilson Staff Development Grant
    - Planning Advisory Nonbook Materials
    - Market Research Division
    - Poetry Committee
    - Southeastern Massachusetts University Libary Advisory Committee
    - Snack Bar
    - Wheaton College Library
    - Last Book Depository
    - Liberation News Service
    - Library Course
    - Library Service Enhancement Program
    - Library Technical Assistant Program
    - New England Academic Library Writing Seminar
    - Nepal
    - New Library, 1971-1978
    - Zagazig University - Egypt
    - Senior Staff
    - Hall, Michael
    - Hartford Times Library
    - Library Bulletin, 1960 (Box 38)
    - Footsteps of History Project
    - Alpex Computer Corporation
    - Compustat Tapes
    - Conservation Internship - Yale (Merrill-Oldham)
    - Brand Report
    - Affirmative Action Report
    - Copyright Group
    - Faculty Status of Librarians
    - Celebrating 100 years of Library Service at UConn, 1992
    - Environment Scanning Team I, II, III, 1995
    - Library Organization Review Team
    - Report of the Selection to Shelf Team Technical Services Workflow
    - Diversity Plan for the Library
    - Proposed Reorg Structure
    - Technical Services and Systems Division
    - A Great Library: Hallmark of a Great University
    - Copyright Group
    - Annual Report (Box 43)
    - Job Descriptions
    - Publicity, 1974-1990
    - Administrative Meeting Minutes, 1978-1983
    - Connecticut Automation Coordination Committee (Box 45)
    - Annual Reports, 1986-1988
      - Art & Design
      - Acquisitions
      - AVM
      - Business Services
      - Cataloging
      - Copy Center
      - F & CMV
      - Government Documents
      - Inter-Library Loan
      - Music
      - Pharmacy
      - Preservations
      - References
      - Serials
      - Special Collections
      - Technical Processes Unit
      - Health Center
      - Law
      - LCCHE
      - Stamford
      - Waterbury
      - Affirmative Action
    - Annual Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 46)
      - Acquisitions
      - Art & Design
      - AV/Microtext
      - Business Services
      - Cataloging
      - CMV
      - Copy Center
      - Government Publications
      - Library Orientation and Instructional Services
      - Map Libary
      - Music Library
      - Pharmacy Library
      - Processing
      - Reserve
      - Reference
      - Serials
      - Special Collections
      - Technical Processing
      - Law Library
      - Health Center
      - School of Business Administration
      - School of Social Work
      - Library at Avery Point and Marine Science
      - Hartford Library
      - Stamford
      - Torrington
      - Waterbury
    - Land Grant Agriculture Public Microfilm Project (Box 47)
    - New Library Move
    - Planning Furniture
    - Sub Basement Shelving
    - Independent Study- correspondence and guidelines
    - Budget
    - Sub Basement and Storage
    - Bibliographic Software
    - Student Labor Allocations
    - Environmental Health and Safety
    - Reports and Surveys, 1990-1991, 1993-1994 (Box 48)
    - Friends of UConn Libraries (Box 49)
    - Reports and Surveys, 1991-1992
    - Reports and Surveys, 1992-1993 (Box 50)
    - Equipment Plan
    - Collections Planning Committee (Box 51)
    - New Library Arrangement of Collections
    - Sub Basement Library Materials
    - Collection Development Policy
    - UCPEA Negotiations
    - CACC: State Libary (Box 52)
    - New Government Publications
    - WCWTW
    - Capra Collection
    - Clarke, Dennis
    - Collections - Black Studies
    - CETA - Official Correspondence
    - CETA - Summer Program
    - Blueprints - Wilbur Cross Library
    - CETA - Grievance Procedures
    - Giberson
    - Management Meetings
    - Access Sub Committee
    - Microtext Committee
    - AACR 2 Staff Training Task Force
    - Joint Operations Land Grant, University
    - Bibliographical Control and Access
    - MRAP Staff Handbook
    - CACC - State Policies
    - Library News
    - Centennial (Box 53)
    - New Library Planning
    - Interdepartmental
    - The Innocent Bystander
    - Report of the Student Employment Task Force
    - Student Employment Programs
    - New England Print Revival
    - Annual Reports, 1985-1986
      - Acquisitions
      - Art
      - Audio Visual Materials
      - Cataloging
      - Circulation
      - Copy Center
      - F & CMU
      - ILL
      - Map
      - GPD
      - Music Library
      - Pharmacy
      - Preservation
      - Reference
      - Special Collections
      - TPU
      - Avery Point
      - Health Center
      - Law
      - Stamford
      - Trecker
      - Waterbury
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1989
      - Acquisitions
      - Art
      - Audio Visual
      - Bibliographic Control
      - Business Services
      - Circulation
      - Collection Development
      - Copy Center
      - F & CMU
      - HMA
      - ILL
      - Map
      - Micro Support
      - Music
      - Pharmacy
      - Preservation
      - RISD
      - Special Collections
      - Circulation Department
      - Directors Advisory Council
      - NELLNET
      - Level B files
      - Survey - Task Force on Access
    - VP for Administration - Giffen
    - Minutes
    - Attachments
    - Activity Report
    - Professional Job Descriptions (Box 55)
    - Managers Handbook (3)
    - Department Training Plans (Box 57)
    - Library Mangers' Calendar/Handbook (2)
    - Accident Reports (Box 59)
    - Affirmative Action
    - Benefits
    - Collective Bargaining
    - Consulting, AR
    - Consulting, Correspondence
    - Consulting, Request for Approval
    - Development Release Time Request
    - Dual State Agency Employment
    - Emergency Closings
    - Exit Interviews
    - Independent Study
    - In-Service Training
    - AAUP - UConn
    - Interview Guidelines
    - Job Descriptions - Other Libraries
    - Jury Duty
    - Job Classification Study
    - Staff Development
    - Organizational Charts
    - Management Update
    - Voluntary Leave and Schedule
    - Job Descriptions (Box 60)
    - Affirmative Action Plan
    - Previous ULA Job Descriptions
    - UConn Policies Labor Relations
    - Contract between State of Connecticut and AFL-CIO
    - Friends of the Library - Correspondence (Box 61)
    - Friends of the Library - Meeting minutes and notices
    - Gateway Library Project
    - Report of Student Employment Task Force
    - Web Publishing Team
    - Publications Committee
    - Library Resource Committee, 1980-1989 (Box 71)
    - Faculty Liason History
    - School of Business Library Task Force
    - Care and Handling of Books (Box 72)
    - Library of Congress Classification System
    - Regional Campuses
      - Avery Point
      - Stamford
      - Waterbury
    - Technical Reports
    - Five Year Plan
    - Charter Inception
    - Tenth Reunion
    - Annual Reports
    - Faculty Publications
    - Friends of UConn
    - Archives
    - IG Davis Project
    - Goals and Objectives
    - Final Schedule of Classes (Box 78)
      - Spring, 1984
      - Fall, 1984
      - Spring, 1985
      - Fall, 1985
      - Spring, 1986
      - Fall, 1986
      - Spring, 1987 (Box 79)
      - Fall, 1987
      - Spring, 1988
      - Fall, 1996
      - Spring, 1997 (Box 80)
      - Fall, 1997
      - Spring, 1998
      - Fall, 1998
    - Budget Guidelines (Box 84)
    - Circulation Policies and Procedures
    - Long Range Planning, 1986
    - Administration and Management
    - Technical Services Reorganization, 1987
- Series III: Vice Provost, undated
  - Paul Kobulnicky, undated
    - Continuous Quality Improvement Benchmarking (Box 39)
    - CQI Team on Sponsored Projects, 1996
    - Office of Grants and Contracts Made of Operation Project
    - Graduate Center Self-Study Initiative
    - Sponsored Projects Information Systems
    - Report of the Government Publications Department Task Force (Box 40)
    - Drafts of Harvest issues
    - Collections Planning Committee (Box 41)
    - Library Departments
      - Government Publications
      - Handicapped Services
      - Historical Manuscripts & Archives
      - Inter Library Loan
      - LOIS
      - Map Room
      - Microtext
      - Music
      - Pharmacy
      - Preservation Program
      - Reference
      - Reserve Room
      - Serials
      - Special Collections
      - Tech Process Unit
      - Public Services
      - Technical Services
    - Computer manuals (Box 42)
    - Purchasing Manual
    - Administration
    - University Memos
    - Meeting Minutes, 1994-1997
    - Computer Programming
    - Express Calc
    - Current Duties Information
    - Focus Group Meeting
    - System Problems
    - Introduction to Windows
    - MS Office
    - MS Access
    - Budget
    - Statistics
    - Special Funding
    - Information Task Force Architecture
    - SPC Members
    - Focus Group Comments
    - UConn 2000
    - Strategic Planning Committee
    - New Org Structure
    - Reorganization
    - NDS Gallery
    - Research Study Guide Information
    - Library Committee Reports (Box 64)
    - Publications
    - Manuals
    - Affirmative Action Plan (Box 68)
    - Sponsored Project Guide
    - Music Library Dedication, 2000
    - Archives and Research Center Planning Committee
    - Report of Collections Planning
    - Investigation of need for Integrated Library System
    - Student Employment Task Force
    - Automation Planning Committee
    - Planning Documents (Box 83)
    - Wilbur Cross Bulletin
    - Faculty Status
  - Brinley Franlin, undated
    - Leadership Council, 2004-2006 (Box 85)
    - Leadership Council, 2006-2008 (Box 86)
- Series IV: Associate Directors, 1970-1978
  - Subseries A: Information and Collection Services ( David Kapp), 1970-1978
    - Advisory Council, undated (Box 14)
    - Administrative Organization, undated
    - Bicentennial, undated
    - Budget, 1976-1978
    - Catalog Department, undated
    - Collection Development, undated
    - Collective Bargaining, undated
    - Committee Meetings, undated
    - Communications Committee, undated
    - Community Service Committee, undated
    - Connecticar, undated
    - Copyright, undated
    - Department Head Meetings, 1974-1975
    - Directories, undated
    - Emergencies, undated
    - Equipment Budget, 1974-1975
    - Exhibits, 1974-1975
    - Exhibit Correspondence, undated
    - Faculty Newsletter, undated
    - Film Program, undated
    - Four Festal Days, undated
    - Graphics, undated
    - Goals and Objectives, undated
    - Government Publications Department, undated
    - Handicapped, undated
    - ILL (Inter-Library Loan), undated
    - Interiors, undated
    - Intern Program, undated
    - Library Course, undated
    - Library Instruction, undated
    - Library Equipment Panel, undated
    - Map Room, undated
    - Maps, undated
    - Media, undated
    - Microfilm Committee, undated
    - Micro/Media, undated
    - Miscellaneous, undated
    - MRAP Implementation Committee, undated
    - MRAP Personnel, undated
    - MRAP Report, undated
    - NASIC, undated
    - NELINET, undated
    - Orientation, undated
    - Orientation, Minutes, undated
    - Pharmacy Library, undated
    - Poetry Readings, undated
    - Policy, undated
    - Publications, undated
    - Publications Committee Minutes, undated
    - Public Borrowers, undated
    - Reserve, undated (Box 15)
    - Reserve / Photocopy / Micro / A/V, undated
    - Security, undated
    - Serials, undated
    - Script, undated
    - Signs, undated
    - Staff Association, undated
    - Staff Association Newsletter, undated
    - Technical Services Meetings, 1976
- Series V: Areas, undated
  - Subseries A: Access Services, undated
  - Subseries B: Collection Services, undated
  - Subseries C: Dodd Research Center, undated, 1965-
    - Dodd Research Center Records, 1965-
  - Subseries D: Information Technology Services, undated
  - Subseries E: Reference and Information Services, 1968-1982
    - Annual reports
      - 1968-1969 (Box 23)
      - 1969-1970
      - 1970-1971
      - 1971-1972
      - 1972-1973
      - 1973-1974
      - 1977-1978
      - 1978-1979
      - 1979-1980
      - 1981-1982
    - Database Guides (Box 62)
    - Homer Jr.
    - Staff Training Guide
    - Resources and Services in support of School of Education
    - Reference department pamphlet file
    - 'How to' guides
    - Job Descriptions
    - Liason program orientation handbook
    - Gateway Libraries Team, 1995
    - Desk Services Manual
    - Desk Services Team
    - Accreditation, School of Business, 1995
    - Guide to Library and Information Centers
    - BLC Virtual Reference
    - Desk Set Files, 1997-2004
    - Level A
    - 24 Hour Study
    - Building Program
  - Subseries F: Regional Campus Libraries, undated
- Series VI: Minutes, 1961-1978
  - Subseries A: Administrative Meetings, 1975-1978
    - 1975 (Box 16)
    - 1976
    - 1977
    - 1978
  - Subseries B: Department Head Meetings, 1961-1975
    - 1961-1967
    - 1971-1975
- Series VII: Staff and Personnel, undated
  - Access, undated (Box 17)
  - Faculty and Staff Newsletter, undated
  - Library News, undated
  - Staff Association, undated
  - Staff Association, Intercom Newsletter, undated
  - Staff Handbooks, undated
  - Staff Lists, undated
  - Staff Notes, undated
  - Subseries A: Bibliographies, 1944-1980
    - Abse, Dannie: Welsh poet and Novelist, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Aging, 1975
    - Aiken, Henry David: Philosopher, 1965
    - Alternatives, 1972
    - Alternative Titles, undated
    - Bacteriology, 1961
    - Bacteriology, 1964
    - Berryman, John: Poet, 1968
    - Black Religion, 1970
    - Black Studies, undated
    - Black Studies, 1970-1971
    - Black Voices in the Sixties, 1970
    - Business Administration, undated
    - Caldwell, Erskine P.: American novelist, 1965
    - Crime and Criminals, undated
    - Connecticut Bicentennial, undated
    - Day-Lewis, C.: British scholar and poet, 1965
    - Education, 1944
    - Education, 1977
    - Engineering Studies, 1965
    - Fitzgerald, Robert: poet and translator, undated
    - Geology, 1963
    - Hecht, Anthony: poet, 1966
    - Ignatow, David: poet, 1966
    - Industrial Organization, Management and Personnel, 1950
    - Literature, English and American, 1972
    - Marketing, undated
    - Microbiology, 1969
    - Nursing, 1967
    - Nursing, 1971
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1975
    - Periodicals, undated
    - Periodicals, 1971
    - Periodicals, Spanish Literature and Philology, 1966
    - Physical Therapy, 1960
    - Puerto Rico, 1976
    - Science and Technology, 1967
    - Social Sciences, 1960
    - Social Science and Humanities, 1968
    - Starbuck, George: poet, 1966
    - Sward, Robert: poet, undated
    - Textiles, 1972
    - Textiles, 1973
    - Vietnam, undated
    - Warren, Robert Penn: novelist and poet, undated
    - Water Resources, 1975
    - Women, undated
    - Women's Studies, 1977
- Series VIII: Book Accession Lists, 1948-1959 (Box 18)
- Series IX: Publications, 1944-1983
  - Subseries B: Exhibits, 1974-1980
    - Dialogues of a New Republic, 1980
    - Harrison, Jon, Photographic Essay, 1974
    - Poetry in the Library and Library Ephemera, 1974
    - Portuguese Gift Book Exhibit, 1977
    - Sculpture in the Library, 1979-1980
    - Amans, Susan (Box 63)
    - Baskets
    - Burke, Matthew
    - CT Women's Hall of Fame
    - Floyd, Jay
    - Hebert, Tom
    - Henderson, Beth
    - Historical Society of Early American Decorations
    - Howes-Stevens, Suzanne
    - Lindsay, Jim
    - Markey, Sally Sargeant
    - Mavor, Salley
    - Rosebrook, Anne
    - Talman, Dana
    - W.E.B DuBois Lihrary
    - Wilhelm, Nancy
    - Wisnewski, Andrea
    - Zaitlin, Diane Bowie
    - Samples
    - Glassblowing
    - HBL 25th Anniversary Project
    - Roger Crossgrove
    - TG files
    - Ann Parker
    - Karen Peterson
    - Myers and Crow
    - Dragons and Musicians
    - Little Red Riding Hood
    - Jos. A. Smith
    - Shane
    - Ogres! Ogres! Ogres!
    - John Magnan
    - John Revill
    - Korean Poster Design (Box 66)
    - Frances Kornbluth
    - A. Kosolapov
    - Kubach
    - Janice Lamotta
    - Judith Lieberman
    - June Linton
    - Franklin Marshall
    - Gus Mazzoca
    - William McCloy
    - Michelle Martin
    - Linda Miller
    - Minutes
    - Manotype Today
    - Barry Moser
    - Rueben Nakian
    - Mary Narbutavicius
    - Naturalists Eye
    - New England Book Show
    - Michele Palmer
    - Deb Pendell
    - Policies and Forum
    - O Write My Name
    - Press Releases (Box 67)
    - Puppet Show
    - Ed Rath
    - Irene Reed
    - Reception
    - Matthew Riley
    - John Revill
    - Ann Rosebrooks
    - Samuel Rosenberg
    - Karin Rosenthal
    - Patricia Rosoff
    - Lucy Sander
    - Sal Scalara
    - Maurice Sendak
    - Quilts Today
    - Robert Sydel
    - Siteline (Smithsonian)
    - Southwesteren Art
    - Sparre
    - Harold Spencer
    - William Stahlman
    - Susan Stanley
    - Structural Graphics
    - Tikvah
    - Tytla
    - Cora Lynn Deibler (Box 73)
    - Angelina Defoca
    - Tomie Depoala
    - Beverly Dickinson
    - Ditardo
    - Dotter
    - Ellen Murphy Dugan
    - Eda Easton
    - Exhibits Committee, 1963-1999
    - Exhibit Damage Claims
    - Michael Adams (Box 74)
    - Jose Alicea
    - Carol Anthony
    - APC Exhibit
    - Artist Review Database
    - Artists Book Exhibit
    - Arts at Black Mountain College
    - Gallery Association
    - Brasher Birds
    - Books for the Next Century
    - Classical Muse(ings)
    - Terry Buckley
    - M.I. Cake
    - David Caroll
    - Pat Carter
    - Jeanne Christie
    - Childrens Book Exhibit
    - Clinton A. Deckert
    - CT Sketchbook
    - Clay Arts East
    - Cortese
    - Cummings and Good
    - Dahlia
    - C. Davidson
    - Exhibit Ideas (Box 75)
    - Exhibit Applications
    - Exhibit Guidelines
    - Exhibit Information
    - Faculty Publications and Awards
    - Want
    - For Freedom
    - Fear
    - Religion
    - Speech
    - From Farm School to University
    - Jaime Ferrer
    - Fiber as Art
    - L.E. Fisher
    - Summer Potters
    - James Flora
    - Kenneth Forman
    - Ruth Gaynes
    - Diane Asseo Grilches
    - Grabowski
    - Gregorian
    - Tom Hebert
    - Bill Hubbell
    - Husky Mania
    - David Kalan
    - Katherin Kadish
    - Mary Kennedy
    - Wilma Keyes
    - Fabrics
    - Art XII (Box 76)
    - Salvatore Gulino
    - Hartford Artisan's Center
    - M. Jabsan-Harden
    - Chet Kempczynski
    - Richard Lethem
    - Charles McCaughtry
    - Jacqueline Lipsky
    - Bob Mannings
    - Jack McConnell
    - Myles Martel
    - Hans Weiss
    - Jewish History Society
    - Terry Ashley
    - Felix Bronner
    - John Bryan
    - Gerard Doudera
    - Laura Eden
    - Peter Crowley
    - Forms
    - Glastonbury Art Association
    - Elizabeth Gourley
    - Donald Moss
    - Peter Nelsa
    - Stephen Petegorsky
    - Lucy Sander Sceery
    - Martha Sielman
    - Photojournalists
    - Rachel Siporin
    - Janet Sarokir
    - Pamela Stockamore
    - Marilyn Rabetz
    - Walter Rabetz
    - A Unique Perspective
    - Harry White
    - Zeke Ziner
    - Zwinger Exhibit
  - Centerbrook Architects Information Cafe, 1998 (Box 82)
  - Subseries C: Guides, 1950-1983
    - Alternatives, 1976 (Box 19)
    - Audio - Visual Aids Center, 1950
    - Black Studies Guide, 1970
    - Book Reviews, undated
    - Government Publications, undated
    - Guide, undated
    - Guide to the UConn Library, 1975
    - Indexing and Abstracting Services, 1970
    - Library Services for Public Borrowers, undated
    - Maps and Directory, undated
    - Music Library, 1978
    - Reference Department, undated
    - UConn. Libraries and Information Centers, undated
    - UConn. Libraries and Information Centers, 1983
    - Welcome to the Wilbur Cross Library, undated
    - Where Are Their Papers?, 1977
    - Wilbur Cross Library, undated
    - Wilbur Cross Library, 1965
    - Wilbur Cross Library, 1966
    - Library Guides (Box 44)
      - American Literature in the 1920s
      - Authors
      - Authors & their works
      - Banned Books
      - Books to film
      - British and American Poets
      - British Poets
      - Drama & Dramatists
      - Education, Higher
      - Education, Research topics
      - Education, Statistics
      - Education, Writing
      - English
      - Gambling
      - Great Britain in the 19th Century
      - Homeless
      - Journalism
      - Literary Criticism
      - Poetry and Early Plays
      - Public School Finance
      - Publishing
      - Scholarship Information
      - Shakespeare's Hamlet
      - Short Stories
      - Statistical Sources
      - Sociology
      - Women in film
      - Writing Requirements
      - Accounting
      - African American Literature
      - African American Reserves
      - African Art
      - African Studies
      - African American History
      - Aging
      - Agricultural Sciences
      - Agricola
      - Agriculture
      - Alcoholism
      - Alternative Press
      - American History
      - American Statistics Index
      - Animal Reproduction
      - Anthropology
      - Library Tours (Box 56)
      - Library Research
      - Library Services
      - Literary Criticism
      - Literature
      - Literature, American and English
      - Literature, Digests
      - Literature, How to Conduct Background Information
      - Magic Logon
      - Marketing Research
      - Map, Reference Collection
      - Materials, Science
      - Netscape
      - New Government Publications
      - Newspapers
      - North American Pre-History
      - Novels and Novelists
      - Nursing and Allied Health
      - Nutrition
      - Patents
      - Physical Therapy
      - Physical Education
      - Places, USA
      - Plays and Playwrights
      - Plays on Audio cassettes
      - Play the Library Game
      - Poets and Poetry
      - Poetry and Poetics, Contemporary
      - Poets reading their own Poetry
      - Policies
      - Political and Public Affairs Collection
      - Political Science (Box 58)
      - Poverty
      - Prints and Printmakers
      - Proceedings, Conferences and Symposiums
      - Pro-cite
      - Psychology